Guide to the Jim Fouratt Papers
Fouratt (Jim) Papers
- Band demos and recordings, 1980 1989; Series IV; 77.42 Linear Feet; (78 boxes); 1347 Audiocassettes; 7 Audiotape Reels
  - Twice A Man, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:58:50 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 64, Item barcode 39002137136405)
  - The Lost Tropics, 1981; 1 Audiocassette; 00:30:19 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. Static, clicks, and pops can be heard. (Box 64, Item barcode 39002137136413)
  - Red Crayola, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:12:38 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Program is distorted at times. (Box 64, Item barcode 39002137136421)
  - Del Lords, 1983; 1 Audiocassette; 00:14:57 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 64, Item barcode 39002137136439)
  - November Group, 1981; 1 Audiocassette; 00:14:08 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 64, Item barcode 39002137136447)
  - Urban Verbs, 1978 August 10; 1 Audiocassette; 00:15:42 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. Audio, at times, sounds thin or unclear. (Box 64, Item barcode 39002137136462)
  - Ike Yard, Crepuscule Release, 1981; 1 Audiocassette; 00:20:41 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. (Box 64, Item barcode 39002137136454)
  - Vivid Section, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:11:04 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Program is distorted at times. (Box 65, Item barcode 39002137135688)
  - Obsession, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:14:44 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. The program is distorted at times. (Box 65, Item barcode 39002137135670)
    A mix of popular music can be heard on the last 34 seconds of the tape.
  - Snap Shot, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:12:40 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. (Box 65, Item barcode 39002137135662)
    Includes "Nothing Ever Comes" and "Sometimes I'd Rather Be With Me".
  - UXA, 1979; 1 Audiocassette; 00:19:57 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. The program is muffled. (Box 65, Item barcode 39002137135654)
    Includes "Social Circle" and "You Saw Me".
  - Units, 1979 October 10; 1 Audiocassette; 00:21:50 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Program is distorted at times. (Box 65, Item barcode 39002137135647)
  - Syntax Eror, 1983; 1 Audiocassette; 00:06:35 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 65, Item barcode 39002137135639)
  - Vivians, 1991; 1 Audiocassette; 00:34:54 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. (Box 65, Item barcode 39002137135696)
    Includes "The Smoker" and "Gold Chain".
  - Personal Effects, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:03:33 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. Static can be heard. The program is distorted at times. (Box 65, Item barcode 39002137135621)
  - Saturn Alley, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:20:18 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. The program is muffled. Static is present. (Box 65, Item barcode 39002137135613)
  - Symbols, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:19:25 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Static is present. The program is distorted at times. Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. (Box 65, Item barcode 39002137135605)
  - The Swift, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:25:45 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. (Box 65, Item barcode 39002137135597)
    Includes "Secrets" and "I Don't Want You".
  - Peter and The Girlfriends, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:07:11 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); High amounts of buzz and static are present. The program is distorted at times. (Box 65, Item barcode 39002137135589)
  - Up All Night, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:28:11 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. (Box 65, Item barcode 39002137135571)
    Includes "It Doesn't Matter" and "Too Shy, Too Bad".
  - The Shades, 1980; 1 Audiocassette; 00:06:49 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. There is a warble heard during the program. (Box 65, Item barcode 39002137135563)
    Includes "Hot Romance" and "Plymouth Rock".
  - The Skunks, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:13:44 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. (Box 65, Item barcode 39002137135555)
  - Nelson Ferrer AD5. Paul Swadkus, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:12:11 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. (Box 65, Item barcode 39002137135548)
    Includes "Out to Lunch" and "La La Song".
  - The Phantoms, 1980; 1 Audiocassette; 00:09:56 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. (Box 65, Item barcode 39002137135530)
    Includes "Political Coup" and "Green Manalishi".
  - The Scientific Americans, 1980; 1 Audiocassette; 00:15:33 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 66, Item barcode 39002137130101)
    A transcribed list of songs is included.
    Meltdown
    Service Dub
    Lemon
    Fascist
  - Ludacer, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:41:47 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. The program is muffled for the last 30 minutes of the program. (Box 66, Item barcode 39002137130093)
    Free Will
    Market Valves
    Class of 77
    Interesting to Feel
    Logic of Love
  - 4 on the Floor, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:02:50 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 66, Item barcode 39002137130085)
  - Cheese, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:11:01 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Static is present. (Box 66, Item barcode 39002137130077)
    Will I Ever Find Out?
    Rose Anne
    Columbia Girls
  - Big Help, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:09:20 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 66, Item barcode 39002137130069)
    it Could Be Tonight
    You're a Gem
    New People
  - Gina Harlow and the Cutthroats, live on stage, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette (Box 66, Item barcode 39002137130051)
    I'm Hot + Wild
    Punks
    Teri Teri Teri
    Ripped T-shirt
  - NoMan, 2 - songs - demo, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:19:03 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Static and dropouts in the audio are present. Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. (Box 66, Item barcode 39002137130044)
  - Gears, 1981; 1 Audiocassette; 00:10:27 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 66, Item barcode 39002137130036)
    The Way I Am
    Don't Worry
    Love Letter
  - Fast Food, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:16:09 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 66, Item barcode 39002137130028)
    Too Cool
    I Still Believe in Us
    Complex Pigeons
    Before My Time
    Umbrella Man
    Insecurity
  - W-2, demo tape, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:10:56 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. (Box 66, Item barcode 39002137130010)
    Dancing on the Head of a Pin
    Toxic Love
    Soho What
    Sprezzatura
  - Untitled, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:18:30 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 66, Item barcode 39002099230006)
  - Neon, 1980; 1 Audiocassette (Box 66, Item barcode 39002099229990)
    Lover in Disguise
    We're Entitled
    Don't Be Afraid of the Night
    No More Heroes
  - The Action, 1981 February; 1 Audiocassette; 00:09:39 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Static is present. The program is distorted at times. (Box 66, Item barcode 39002099229982)
    Fashion Forward
    Just Let Me Rock
    Till I See You Again
    She's Got My Heart
  - Viscous Bulb I, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:23:06 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is muffled. Static is present. The program is distorted at times. Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. (Box 66, Item barcode 39002099229974)
    A transcribed list of contents is included.
    Viscous Bulb I
    Deutschalingus
    Soldier Life
    Donna Reed
    Warrior
  - Thin Ice, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:08:06 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 66, Item barcode 39002099229966)
    Tell Me Why
    Mr. Lonely
    Suspicious
  - Treble Boys, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:10:21 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. (Box 66, Item barcode 39002099229958)
    How Do Lovers Do It
    Julie-Ann
    I Can't Hold On
    The Girls Have Gone Away
  - Squeaky Clean - Rockabilly, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:11:28 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 66, Item barcode 39002099229941)
    Oh Boy
    Right String Baby
    Bye Bye Love
    Rock Boppin' Baby
    Rip It Up
  - Hard Facts, 1983; 1 Audiocassette; 00:14:05 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 66, Item barcode 39002099229933)
    Teenage Love
    Hard Facts
    Chicken Parts
    Fall in Line
  - Arthur Monroe Zone, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:11:48 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 67, Item barcode 39002137168523)
    In My Skin
    Lincoln
    Scrutiny
  - U.S. Ape, 1980; 1 Audiocassette; 00:11:36 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Static is present. (Box 67, Item barcode 39002137168614)
    accepted
    nervous
    who wants to go?
    girls with crewcuts
  - IC's, 1980 April 4 1980 April 5; 1 Audiocassette; 00:16:49 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. (Box 67, Item barcode 39002137168606)
    American Express
    Jamaica Jump
    Bellel - 5
    Night by the River
  - 4/4, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:32:04 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. Static is present. (Box 67, Item barcode 39002137168598)
    A mix of music from several artists was recorded in the last 16 minutes of the program.
  - Lord of the Strings, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:13:24 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. (Box 67, Item barcode 39002137168580)
  - Idle Sponsor, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 01:31:53 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. Static and dropouts in the audio are present. Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. (Box 67, Item barcode 39002137168572)
    Songs listed include "Easy for You to Say" and "In + Out of Love".
    A letter from Richard Fantina is included. It reads, in part: "Jim, I hope you enjoy this tape of 2 songs by Idle Sponsor. I can't think of another New York band that plays this kind of music. The band has been together for over three years but they only play out around twice a year. I'm trying to get them to become more visible because I really believe in their music. I hope you can find a slot for them at the Underground. If you have any questions or comments please call me...Thanks, Richard Fantina.
    A mix of popular music was recorded at about 46 minutes until the end of the tape.
  - The Very Few, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; The tape is blank. No files were digitized. (Box 67, Item barcode 39002137168564)
  - Tally-Ho, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:29:30 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. The last 15 minutes of the program sounds muffled. Static is present. Dropouts in the audio are present. (Box 67, Item barcode 39002137168556)
  - The Scene (demonstration tape), 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:10:41 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Dolby was decoded during playback. (Box 67, Item barcode 39002137168549)
    We're Not Kids Anymore
    Cynthia
    Follow Up Single
  - Shrug, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:08:28 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Static can be heard. (Box 67, Item barcode 39002137168515)
  - Silence - Zero, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:20:05 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Speed fluctuations are present near the end of the program. (Box 67, Item barcode 39002137168531)
    Don't Lean Out
    I'm Feeling Like a Strange Orangutang
    Save My Life
    Hong Tha
    Arrival
  - Terrorists, 1979; 1 Audiocassette; 00:09:55 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. (Box 67, Item barcode 39002137168507)
  - The Symptoms, 1980 April 20; 1 Audiocassette; 00:14:48 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. (Box 67, Item barcode 39002137168499)
    Simple Sabotage
    Wide Awake
    Giant Step
    Elegy for Maggie
    World of Business
  - Faculty Party, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:25:02 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 67, Item barcode 39002137168481)
  - THE ME?S, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:14:07 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 67, Item barcode 39002137168473)
  - Hi-Fi - Live at Max's "Deli-Rock", 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:16:42 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. High amounts of buzz are present. (Box 67, Item barcode 39002137168465)
  - Scientific Americans, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 01:03:09 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. Static is present. (Box 67, Item barcode 39002137168457)
  - V, rough mix, 1981 July 20; 1 Audiocassette; 00:13:03 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 68, Item barcode 39002099224744)
    ich Liebe
    Sirens
    Skitzed
    Niteland
  - Strange Boutique, 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:21:20 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 68, Item barcode 39002099224751)
    in the lonely trees
    a happy death
    drown
    quicksand minds
  - Pinhead - You Don't Like Me, Do Ya?, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:26:02 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. Static can be heard. (Box 68, Item barcode 39002099224769)
    Almost Human
    Back to the Womb
    Where are You?
    Little Rocker
    Citizen
    You Don't Like Me Do Ya'?
    Stealing Your Wife
  - Tim Warren, Disc Jockey Audition Tape, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 01:01:05 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. Static is present. Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. (Box 68, Item barcode 39002099224777)
  - Face of the Future, Manhattan Project, 4-track demos, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:32:51 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. (Box 68, Item barcode 39002099224785)
  - Face of the Future, Manhattan Project, 4-track demos, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:12:46 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 68, Item barcode 39002099224793)
    A transcribed list of songs include: "Los Alamos", "By + By" and "I Believe".
  - Los Microwaves, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:16:58 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Static can be heard. The program is distorted at times. The program is in silence from 00:15:33-00:15:56 and from 00:15:57-00:17:45. The program was recorded at a very high level for the first 15 minutes of the program. (Box 68, Item barcode 39002099224801)
  - The Hitites, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:25:11 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. (Box 68, Item barcode 39002099224819)
    Tracking Cheetahs
    Nothing Nowhere
    Yick Ooohh
    Adoption Center
    Kock Suki
    Jerk City
    Wait by the Window
    Dilemma
    Hound of Hell
    Hollywood
  - Kind, 1981; 1 Audiocassette; 00:17:19 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. (Box 68, Item barcode 39002099224827)
    Find a Way
    Years Gone By
    New Age Madness
    Over the Border
  - A Few - It's A Wonderful Life, 1985; 1 Audiocassette; 01:15:30 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Static is present. The program is distorted at times. The program is in silence from 00:16:50-00:17:11. The left channel audio is low from 00:35:17-00:55:41. (Box 68, Item barcode 39002099224835)
  - Tim Warren, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 01:01:53 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. Static is present. High amounts of buzz are present. (Box 68, Item barcode 39002099224843)
    A transcribed note on the cassette liner reads: Dear Jim, Please consider this tape if you are ever in need of a FUN Rock 'n' Roll d.j. I've given up hope with "new" music and regressed (happi[l]y).
  - The Delusions, Drink And Be Mary, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:46:56 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. Static can be heard. High amounts of buzz are present. (Box 68, Item barcode 39002099224850)
  - EQ'd, 1981; 1 Audiocassette; 00:09:47 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. The program is distorted at times. (Box 68, Item barcode 39002099224868)
    A transcribed song list includes: "Gridlock", "Gerrymander" and "Scream/Industrial"
  - Max Jersey, Home Movies, recorded "live" at Dreamland, 1980 January 31; 1 Audiocassette; 00:30:24 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. Static can be heard. High amounts of hiss are present. Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. (Box 68, Item barcode 39002099224876)
  - If Then Why - "The Graduation" - E. P., 1983; 1 Audiocassette; 00:19:24 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Static is present. The program is distorted at times. (Box 68, Item barcode 39002099224884)
    Counter Circular
    His Still Day
    One Man Warrior
    We Move
  - New York Space Ensemble, 1981; 1 Audiocassette; 00:07:59 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. (Box 68, Item barcode 39002099224892)
  - Sighs Five, 1980; 1 Audiocassette; 00:24:38 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 68, Item barcode 39002099224900)
    Goose Bumps
    Betamax
    Sniper
    Eraser
    Which Rich
    Their Eyes
  - Standard Deviation, 1984; 1 Audiocassette; 00:12:31 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Static can be heard during the program. (Box 69, Item barcode 39002099224397)
    A transcribed list of songs includes: "Nerves", "Insignificant" and "Major Needs".
  - Mood Elevators, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:10:42 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. (Box 69, Item barcode 39002099224405)
    A transcribed list of songs includes: "Moment of Pleasure", "This is the Moment" and "Nearer". The latter two songs were recorded live.
  - Tiger Beats, Live at Max's, 1980 June 6; 1 Audiocassette; 00:57:53 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Static can be heard. The program is distorted at times. Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. The program fades in and out for the first 28 minutes. (Box 69, Item barcode 39002099224413)
  - The Very Few, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:09:37 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. (Box 69, Item barcode 39002099224421)
    A transcribed list of songs includes: "The Very Few", "The Party's Over", and "Here I Go Again".
  - The Gangster Choir, 1981; 1 Audiocassette; 00:06:49 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Static is present. The program is distorted at times. (Box 69, Item barcode 39002099224439)
    Includes the song "Tenement Lover"
  - The Heartbeats - Demo, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:10:04 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 69, Item barcode 39002099224447)
    A transcribed list of songs includes: "Can't Face Her", "All American Girl" and "Dancin' Shoes"
  - Johnny Supreme + The Immortals, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:20:32 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 69, Item barcode 39002099224454)
  - Tea Time, Closer - Triumph of Reason, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:10:22 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Static can be heard. The program is distorted at times. (Box 69, Item barcode 39002099224462)
  - Ike Yard / Treated Drum Tracks - Stunted and Metal African, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:25:16 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. High amounts of buzz is present. (Box 69, Item barcode 39002099224470)
  - The B-Girls, 1981; 1 Audiocassette; 00:28:32 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is in silence from 00:06:56-00:08:19. The program is distorted at times. There is a warble in the program. The program is muffled from 00:08:19-00:28:32. (Box 69, Item barcode 39002099224488)
    Songs include "The Boys Are Drinkin'" and "Two Hearts"
  - Things That Fall Down, Demo/Rough Mix, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:10:26 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. Static is present. There is an imbalance in the audio. The program is muffled. Aduio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. (Box 69, Item barcode 39002099224496)
    A transcribed list of songs includes: "Day Out", "Things That Fall Down" and "Funky Stuff"
  - Riddley Walker, 1983; 1 Audiocassette; 00:05:50 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. (Box 69, Item barcode 39002099224504)
    Songs include "Vivien Leigh" and "Uncle from America"
  - Twilites, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:14:33 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. Static is present. (Box 69, Item barcode 39002099224512)
    Confused
    Drop Out of Time
    Mirrors
    I Don't Know What Have Is
  - The Pseudos, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:11:05 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. Static can be heard. High amounts of hum are present. (Box 69, Item barcode 39002099224520)
    A transcribed list of songs includes: "Man in the Middle", "Canal" and "Cruising Through Life"
  - Sweet Talk, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:11:18 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. (Box 69, Item barcode 39002099224538)
    A transcribed list of songs includes: "Sweet Talker, Street Walker", "Ooh Yeah" and "All of My Life"
  - Cuddly Toys, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:05:19 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. (Box 69, Item barcode 39002099224546)
  - Nude Ants, 1983; 1 Audiocassette; 00:22:26 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. (Box 69, Item barcode 39002099224553)
    Spys
    So Fine
    Crocodile
    Love of the South
    Whipped and Chained
    I Can't Remember
  - E-Static (studio/live), 1979; 1 Audiocassette; 00:26:46 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. Audio is unbalanced,at times, in the last 16 minutes of the program. Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. (Box 70, Item barcode 39002099224231)
    A transcribed list of songs is included with this audiocassette.
    Modern Girl
    Stranger
    The Music
    Car Accident
    Fat Debby
    Flattery Active
    Standing at the Brink
    Paranoid
    Be True
    Dead Father Talk
    Dancing
  - Extreme Unction (Live) [rehearsal studio tape], 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:10:30 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 70, Item barcode 39002099224215)
    Songs transcribed on the tape include: "Juvenile Success", "Neonglow" and "Hit me in the Heart"
  - Candy / Doug, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:10:13 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 70, Item barcode 39002099224223)
  - Michael Blaise, 1979; 1 Audiocassette; 00:28:40 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 70, Item barcode 39002099224249)
  - Joe Hampton + the Extremes, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:10:33 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 70, Item barcode 39002099224256)
    A transcribed list of songs include: "Scrambled", "Phone to Rome" and "Dogs in Traffic"
  - Junk Rock, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:12:07 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. (Box 70, Item barcode 39002099224264)
  - Cann Cann, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:09:53 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Audio is unbalanced at times. Static is present. The program is distorted at times. Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. (Box 70, Item barcode 39002099224272)
  - Cold Steel Rock, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:24:15 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. (Box 70, Item barcode 39002099224280)
    Don't Have Time
    Vanilla Waffer
    You Got Me
    The Devil Winds
    Skin Bracer
    Miss Hargrave
  - The Dates, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:08:30 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. Audio, at times, is hollow or unclear. (Box 70, Item barcode 39002099224298)
  - Futants, 1979; 1 Audiocassette; 00:07:17 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. Audio, at times, sounds hollow or unclear. (Box 70, Item barcode 39002099224306)
    Dead City
    Alien
    The Amusement Park
    Blackout Music
    Martin Music
    Nouse w/out Permission
  - Fast Food, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:17:40 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Static is present. (Box 70, Item barcode 39002099224314)
  - Molls, 1980 1989; 1 Audiocassette; 00:49:39 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); There i a gap in the program from 00:27:14-00:30:21. Static is present. The program is distorted at times. (Box 70, Item barcode 39002099224322)
    Includes "We're Not Gonna Take It"